
=== Deploying to 'metodo1dia-app'...

i  deploying functions
i  functions: preparing codebase default for deployment
i  functions: ensuring required API cloudfunctions.googleapis.com is enabled...
i  functions: ensuring required API cloudbuild.googleapis.com is enabled...
i  artifactregistry: ensuring required API artifactregistry.googleapis.com is enabled...
!  functions: package.json indicates an outdated version of firebase-functions. Please upgrade using npm install --save firebase-functions@latest in your functions directory.
!  functions: Please note that there will be breaking changes when you upgrade.
i  functions: Loading and analyzing source code for codebase default to determine what to deploy
Serving at port 8289

i  extensions: ensuring required API firebaseextensions.googleapis.com is enabled...
i  functions: preparing functions directory for uploading...
i  functions: packaged C:\Users\Lenovo\Desktop\metodo 1 dia perfil premium 2\functions (38.35 KB) for uploading
+  functions: functions source uploaded successfully
i  functions: updating Node.js 22 (1st Gen) function getContentUrl(us-central1)...
+  functions[getContentUrl(us-central1)] Successful update operation.
Function URL (getContentUrl(us-central1)): https://us-central1-metodo1dia-app.cloudfunctions.net/getContentUrl
!  functions: No cleanup policy detected for repositories in us-central1. This may result in a small monthly bill as container images accumulate over time.

Error: Functions successfully deployed but could not set up cleanup policy in location us-central1. Pass the --force option to automatically set up a cleanup policy or run 'firebase functions:artifacts:setpolicy' to manually set up a cleanup policy.
